Finding Aid for James J. Duderstadt Papers
Bentley Historical Library
- Paper Documents
  - Speeches and Accompanying Material, 1981-1996; 6.5 linear feet
    - 1986
      - Center for Research on Teaching and Learning New Faculty, September 9, 1986 (Box 2)
      - Experimental Research in Electronic Submission Program Talk, September 10, 1986 (Box 2)
      - E.O. Lawrence Award, September 11, 1986 (Box 2)
      - Alumni Merit Scholars, September 15, 1986 (Box 2)
      - Alumni Talks, September 18, 1986 (Box 2)
      - Engineering NAC Meeting, September 26, 1986 (Box 2)
      - Comments, October 4, 1986 (Box 2)
      - Dentistry, October 13, 1986 (Box 2)
      - Yale Alumni Association of Michigan, October 30, 1986 (Box 2)
      - National Honor Society, November 10, 1986 (Box 2)
      - Dentistry, November 20, 1986 (Box 2)
      - IBM Luncheon, November 20, 1986 (Box 2)
      - Generic Leadership Address, December 4, 1986 (Box 2)
      - Plan to Respond to the Challenge of Leadership, December 4 (Box 2)
      - Generic Leadership Address, December 11, 1986 (Box 22)
      - Masons, May 27, 1986 (Box 22)
      - Iacocca-Fraser Commission, May 29, 1986 (Box 22)
      - Majoring Hanging Decisions, June 1986 (Box 22)
      - HTS Discussions, June 3, 1986 (Box 22)
      - Budget Priorities Committee, June 26, 1986 (Box 22)
      - All Campus Development Staff, June 27, 1986 (Box 22)
      - Medical School, September 2, 1986 (Box 22)
      - Art Faculty Meeting, September 2, 1986 (Box 22)
      - Masons, September 7, 1986 (Box 22)
      - Questions, September 7, 1986 (Box 22)
      - Educating for a World of Technological Change, September 7, 1986 (Box 22)
      - The Future of Engineering Education, September 7, 1986 (Box 22)
      - LSA Faculty Meeting, September 17, 1986 (Box 22)
      - Alumni Talk, September 22, 1986 (Box 22)
      - UM Dearborn, October 22, 1986 (Box 22)
    - 1987
      - Sets of Talks, 1987 (Box 2)
      - Physics, January 21, 1987 (Box 2)
      - Research Excellence Fund Symposium, February 12, 1987 (Box 2)
      - Space Physics Research Lab, February 13, 1987 (Box 2)
      - Alumni Talk, February 15, 1987 (Box 2)
      - High Tech in Michigan, March 1, 1987 (Box 2)
      - NIH Predoctoral Genetics Training Grant (Box 2)
      - Terman Talk, March 10, 1987 (Box 2)
      - United States / Japan Conference, April 14, 1987 (Box 2)
      - Let's Do It Right, April 15, 1987 (Box 2)
      - Yale Talk, April 16, 1987 (Box 2)
      - Alumni Talk, May 7, 1987 (Box 2)
      - Educating For a World of Change, May 8, 1987 (Box 2)
      - Role of Research University in Undergraduate Education, May (Box 2)
      - Michigan High Tech, May 1987 (Box 2)
      - Challenge of Equal Opportunity, June 5, 1987 (Box 2)
      - National Nursing Symposium, June 11, 1987 (Box 2)
      - National Center for Manufacturing Sciences, July 20, 1987 (Box 2)
      - Integrated Technology Instruction Center, August 1987 (Box 2)
      - Michigan's Challenge: The Age of Knowledge, Fall 1987 (Box 2)
      - Challenge of Diversity and Excellence, September 2, 1987 (Box 2)
      - Freshman Convocation, September 10, 1987 (Box 2)
      - Challenge of Leadership: A Mission of the 21st Century, September 20, 1987 (Box 2)
      - Senate Assembly, September 21, 1987 (Box 2)
      - Grand Rapids Economics Club, October 1987 (Box 2)
      - Educating for a World of Change / Grad School Conference, November 14, 1987 (Box 2)
      - Enrollment Study, November 16, 1987 (Box 2)
      - Challenge of Diversity and Excellence, December 7, 1987 (Box 2)
      - Parent's Orientation, December 31, 1987 (Box 2)
      - Ethics and Values Conference, March 7, 1987 (Box 22)
      - "Terman" Talk 0.9, March 10, 1987 (Box 22)
      - Education for the Age of Knowledge, March 23, 1987 (Box 22)
      - Master Notes: The Age of Knowledge, April 2, 1987 (Box 22)
      - US-Japan Conference, April 14, 1987 (Box 22)
      - Some Thoughts, April 28, 1987 (Box 22)
      - Alumni Talk, May 5, 1987 (Box 22)
      - Educating for a World of Change, May 8, 1987 (Box 22)
      - Senate Assembly-5/18, May 17, 1987 (Box 22)
      - Welcome, May 18, 1987 (Box 22)
      - Undergraduate Education, May 31, 1987 (Box 22)
      - Undergraduate Enrollments, June 9, 1987 (Box 22)
      - Michigan Conference on Industrial Competitivess (sic), June 16, 1987 (Box 22)
      - Development Staff, June 30, 1987 (Box 22)
      - Business Administration, September 17, 1987 (Box 22)
      - Senate Assembly, September 24, 1987 (Box 22)
      - Western Michigan, September 25, 1987 (Box 22)
      - West Quad, October 25, 1987 (Box 22)
      - The Diversity Agenda 1.1, December 7, 1987 (Box 22)
    - 1988
      - Academic Affairs (Box 2)
      - Commencements (Box 2)
      - Michigan Mandate (Box 2)
      - Martin Luther King Event, January 12, 1988 (Box 2)
      - Academic Affairs, January 1988 (Box 2)
      - Medical Center Information Technology, February 4, 1988 (Box 2)
      - SSC Testimony, February 16, 1988 (Box 2)
      - Physics, February 20, 1988 (Box 2)
      - Freshman Presentation, February 22, 1988 (Box 2)
      - Future of Engineering, February 22, 1988 (Box 2)
      - Graduate Education, February 22, 1988 (Box 2)
      - Overheads: Challenge of Leadership: A Mission for the 21st Century, March 12, 1988 (Box 2)
      - Traxler / Bloch, March 14, 1988 (Box 2)
      - Leadership Evaluation, March 14, 1988 (Box 2)
      - Undergraduate Education; Role of Alumni; Student-Athletes; State Legislature, March 15, 1988 (Box 2)
      - Overheads: Challenge of Leadership: A Mission for the 21st Century, March 28, 1988 (Box 2)
      - Overheads: Michigan Plan: A Strategy for the Enhancement of Excellence through Diversity, March 28, 1988 (Box 2)
      - Questions, April 11, 1988 (Box 2)
      - Science and Engineering Education for the 21st Century: Challenge of Change in Age of Knowledge, April 15, 1988 (Box 2)
      - Alumni Talk, Philadelphia, April 15, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Yale Science and Engineering, April 16, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Overheads: A Challenge of Leadership: A Mission for the 21st Century, April 19, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Michigan Plan; Viewgraphs; Version 1.2, April 22, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Ethics in Higher Education (Book), April 25, 1988 (Box 3)
      - College of Engineering Graduation, April 30, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Public Service and the Public Research University, April 1988 (Box 3)
      - Michigan Plan; Version 1.4, May 1, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Notes on Sculley, May 8, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Educating for World of Change, May 8, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Office of Academic Affairs Summary, May 10, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Undergraduate Education Address, May 16, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Fiscal Year 1988-89 Budget Presentation, May 20, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Network Computing Forum Welcome, May 25, 1988 (Box 3)
      - United States Department of Energy Visit Video, May 31, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Brief History of State Capital Outlay Appropriations for Higher Education, May 1988 (Box 3)
      - Athena Alumnae Award, June 3, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Medical School Commencement, June 3, 1988 (Box 3)
      - National Science Foundation and Mich. Strategic Fund, June 8, 1988 (Box 3)
      - National Nursing Symposium, June 11, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Freshman Convocation, June 13, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Medicine-Computer II, June 14, 1988 (Box 3)
      - IBM Dean's Conference, June 14, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Blanchard-Tuition, June 30, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Council on Academic Affairs Summer Retreat, August 4, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Provost Keynote, San Diego, August 8, 1988 (Box 3)
      - IFS Reception, August 30, 1988 (Box 3)
      - National Science Foundation Luncheon, August 30, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Future's Talk, September 2, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Mirlyn, September 20, 1988 (Box 3)
      - If Harvard is the Michigan of the East..., October, 1988 (Box 3)
      - State of the University, October 3, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Inauguration, October 4, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Historically Black, Predominately Hispanic Colleges, October 5, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Faculty Awards and the Michigan Challenge, October 7, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Dean Kickoff Event, October 7, 1988 (Box 3)
      - IFS Reception, October 7, 1988 (Box 3)
      - National Science Foundation NET, October 7, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Dedication of Canham Natorium, October 16, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Hispanic Alumni, October 21, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Booth Newspapers, October 28, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Version 2.2, November, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Frankel Center for Judiac Studies, November 1988 (Box 3)
      - Brass Hat Reception, November 9, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Wilson Inauguration, October 16, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Football Bust, November 28, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Michigan Plan, Version 2.2, November, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 3)
      - MLK Talks, January 1988 (Box 22)
      - Athletes Reception, February 7, 1988 (Box 22)
      - U.S. Department of Energy Public Hearing on SSC, February 16, 1988 (Box 22)
      - Remarks, March 8, 1988 (Box 22)
      - Welcome, March 23, 1988 (Box 22)
      - Questions, March 23, 1988 (Box 22)
      - The Michigan Plan, March 24, 1988 (Box 22)
      - Undergraduate Education, April 5, 1988 (Box 22)
      - Yale S&E Talk, April 15, 1988 (Box 22)
      - Dean's Dinner, April 24, 1988 (Box 22)
      - Remarks, May 21, 1988 (Box 22)
      - Statement of James J. Duderstadt, June 10, 1988 (Box 22)
      - Freshman Convocation, September 6, 1988 (Box 22)
      - The Michigan Mandate-Senate Assembly, September 19, 1988 (Box 22)
      - Congressional Delegation, September 20, 1988 (Box 22)
      - General Talk, September 22, 1988 (Box 22)
      - Leadership Network, September 23, 1988 (Box 22)
      - The Challenge of Change, October 6, 1988 (Box 22)
      - Alumni Talk, October 12, 1988 (Box 22)
      - Prigogine, December 9, 1988 (Box 22)
      - Thomas Kuhn, December 9, 1988 (Box 22)
    - 1989
      - Major Presentations for and List of Talks, 1989-1990 (Box 4)
      - Athletics (Box 4)
      - Commencements, May and December (Box 4)
      - Michigan Mandate, 2 folders (Box 4)
      - Set of Speeches (Box 4)
      - Lunch and Learn, January 12, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Detroit Economics Club, February 13, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Football Building Kickoff, February 17, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Legislative / Alumni / Lansing, March 14, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Honors Convocation, March 19, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Native American Pow-Wow, March 18, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Henry Russel Lecture, March 21, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Continuity and Chaos, March 24, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Women's Issues, March 28, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Presidential Initiatives Fund Symposium, March 28, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Legatus Talk, March 30, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Team Building, April 5, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Phi Beta Kappa, April 8, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Satellite Broadcast, April 9, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Basketball Bust, April 10, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Senate Republican Caucus, April 25, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Ann Arbor Rotary Club, May 17, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Cal Tech Commencement, June 16, 1989 (Box 4)
      - NAACP Convention, September 8, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Corporate Program Remarks, September 9, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Chemistry Building Dedication, September 15, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Citizen's Research Council, September 19, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Cleveland Lunch, September 27, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Educom, October 17, 1989 (Box 4)
      - State of the University, October 2, 1989 (Box 4)
      - New York Business Leaders, October 5, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Speech Topics, December 3, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Tuition Press Conference, December 3, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Women's Issues: An Agenda For Action, March 28, 1989 (Box 22)
      - Continuity, Change, and Chaos, April 8, 1989 (Box 22)
      - Preparing for a Future of Change, June 16, 1989 (Box 22)
      - The Role of the Research University in Undergraduate Education, September 26, 1989 (Box 22)
    - 1990
      - Set of Speeches (Box 4)
      - Michigan Mandate Two-Year Status Report (Box 4)
      - President's Council / Forums (Box 4)
      - Requests for Michigan Mandate (Box 4)
      - Senate Assembly (Box 4)
      - Speeches Pertaining to State Relations (Box 4)
      - Science Club Joint Lecture, January 16, 1990 (Box 4)
      - Cranbrook, February 11, 1990 (Box 4)
      - Congressional Delegation, February 28, 1990 (Box 4)
      - Flint Rotary, March 30, 1990 (Box 4)
      - Alumni Association Induction, May 12, 1990 (Box 4)
      - Automotive Conference, April 2, 1990 (Box 4)
      - Midland Adult Education, April 5, 1990 (Box 4)
      - Alliance Conference, April 6, 1990 (Box 4)
      - Democracy Symposium, April 5, 1990 (Box 4)
      - Basketball Bust, April 9, 1990 (Box 4)
      - United Way Leadership Conference, April 9, 1990 (Box 4)
      - Senior Leaders Luncheon, April 26, 1990 (Box 4)
      - Michigan Science and Technology Quest, April 27, 1990 (Box 4)
      - Lamberto Cesari Memorial, April 27, 1990 (Box 4)
      - Campus Information Center Meeting Welcome, May 3, 1990 (Box 4)
      - English Commencement, May 5, 1990 (Box 4)
      - Bo Farewell Dinner, May 6, 1990 (Box 4)
      - President's Club / Spring Weekend, May 18, 1990 (Box 4)
      - Ann Arbor Rotary, May 15, 1990 (Box 4)
      - Service Awards Dinner, June 6, 1990 (Box 4)
      - Hartford Memorial Baptist Church, June 24, 1990 (Box 4)
      - Faculty Convocation, September 24, 1990 (Box 4)
      - State of the University, September 24, 1990 (Box 4)
      - Wallenberg Lecture, September 25, 1990 (Box 5)
      - Ann Arbor Chamber of Commerce, September 26, 1990 (Box 5)
      - Ehrlicher Room Dedication, October 4, 1990 (Box 5)
      - Michigan Ethnic Heritage Studies, October 5, 1990 (Box 5)
      - Rackham Administration Office, October 17, 1990 (Box 5)
      - Sante Fe Institute, November 1, 1990 (Box 5)
      - AFL-CIO, December 7, 1990 (Box 5)
      - America at the Crossroads: The Challenge of Science Education, Joint Meeting Science Research Club and Sigma Xi Scientific Research Society, January 16, 1990 (Box 22)
      - A Heritage of Leadership: The Challenge of Change, June 1, 1990 (Box 22)
      - Michigan Mandate: The Hope, Promise, and Challenge of Multicultural Society, June 24, 1990 (Box 22)
      - Ann Arbor Chamber Commerce, September 26, 1990 (Box 22)
      - The Michigan Mandate: To Build a Multicultural Learning Community for the 21st Century, October 5, 1990 (Box 22)
      - Public Education in America: Crisis in an Age of Knowledge, November 9, 1990 (Box 22)
    - 1991
      - Michigan Mandate Three-Year Status Report (Box 5)
      - Basketball Bust, March 18, 1991 (Box 5)
      - Catholic Men's Breakfast, April 2, 1991 (Box 5)
      - Junior League, April 9, 1991 (Box 5)
      - Commencement, May 4, 1991 (Box 5)
      - Senate Assembly, May 20, 1991 (Box 5)
      - Forum on Educational Competitiveness, May 20, 1991 (Box 5)
      - Class of 1995 Welcome, September 1, 1991 (Box 5)
      - Freshman Parent Orientation, September 1, 1991 (Box 5)
      - Graduate Convocation, September 4, 1991 (Box 5)
      - Plymouth Northville Alumni, October 3, 1991 (Box 5)
      - Ann Arbor Chamber of Commerce, October 15, 1991 (Box 5)
      - Ann Arbor Rotary, October 30, 1991 (Box 5)
      - The Political Correctness Debate: Achieving a Balance Between Academics and Social Responsibilities, May 20, 1991 (Box 22)
      - A Michigan Education, September 27, 1991 (Box 22)
      - A Wake-Up Call to America, October 15, 1991 (Box 22)
      - The External Environment of the University, November 18, 1991 (Box 22)
    - 1991-1992
      - Sigma Xi / Science Research Club (Box 5)
      - Lansing Rotary, January 24, 1992 (Box 5)
      - Public Service and the Public University, August 1992 (Box 22)
      - Talking Points of James Duderstadt to Michigan Community College Presidents, September 15, 1992 (Box 22)
      - Redrawing the Boundaries, November 16, 1992 (Box 22)
    - 1993
      - Sigma Xi Scientific Research Society, January 19, 1993 (Box 22)
      - A University Enterprise Zone, February 9, 1993 (Box 22)
      - GM Volunteer Spirit Awards, March 31, 1993 (Box 22)
      - Educating for the Age of Knowledge, May 4, 1993 (Box 22)
      - A China Odyssey, June 2, 1993 (Box 22)
      - Freshman Convocation, September 1993 (Box 22)
      - Graduate Student Convocation, September 8, 1993 (Box 22)
    - 1994
      - The University of the 21st Century, May 23, 1994 (Box 22)
      - Introduction and Presentation of the Raoul Wallenberg Medal to His Holiness the Dalai Lama, April 21, 1994 (Box 22)
      - Council on Continuous Improvement, July 8, 1994 (Box 22)
      - New Student Convocation, September 1, 1994 (Box 22)
      - Faculty Orientation Luncheon, September 1, 1994 (Box 22)
    - 1995
      - Martin Luther King Day Opening Remarks, January 16, 1995 (Box 22)
      - Introduction of Steven Olswang, January 22, 1996 (Box 22)
      - Remarks for Symposium "Commitment to Collaboration: New Strategies for Community-Based Development in Detroit,", February 2, 1996 (Box 22)
      - Parke-Davis presentation on Michigan Agenda for Women, March 6, 1995 (Box 22)
      - Reinventing the University, March 8, 1995 (Box 22)
      - Business to Business, March 16, 1995 (Box 22)
      - Diversity and Excellence: The Challenge for a 21st Century World, March 21, 1995 (Box 22)
      - Women: Transforming Higher Education Conference, March 31, 1995 (Box 22)
      - Ann Arbor: An Economic Engine for the 21st Century, April 6, 1995 (Box 22)
      - Salk Anniversary, April 12, 1995 (Box 22)
      - Michigan Industrial Expo '95, April 11, 1995 (Box 22)
      - Jewish Federation Forum, April 10, 1995 (Box 22)
      - President's Advisory Group, remarks, May 5, 1995 (Box 22)
      - The Government-University Research Partnership: Beyond the Endless Frontier...?, May 16, 1995 (Box 22)
      - 27th CIRP International Seminar on Manufacturing Systems, remarks, May 22, 1995 (Box 22)
      - Dzero High-Energy Physics Collaboration Workshop, June 12, 1995 (Box 22)
      - State of the University Address, September 1995 (Box 22)
      - United Way Kick-Off Luncheon, September 18, 1995 (Box 22)
      - A Vision for the 21st Century: Beyond "The Leaders and Best"..., September 1995 (Box 22)
      - Outline for Senate Assembly, September 25, 1995 (Box 22)
      - Rapid Changes in Business Technology: How Can Higher Education Help?, November 21, 1995 (Box 22)
      - Groundbreaking for renovation of the University Health Service Building, remarks, December 6, 1995 (Box 22)
    - 1996
      - Diversity, January 1996 (Box 22)
      - Michigan's Future in a Word: Education, February 2, 1996 (Box 22)
      - The Jerome B. Wiesner Symposium, February 26, 1996 (Box 22)
      - Senate Assembly, March 1996 (Box 22)
      - Commencement Address at University Graduate Exercises, May 3, 1996 (Box 22)
      - Welcome comments for the 1996 Annual Meeting of the American Physical Society Division of Atomic, Molecular and Optical Physics, May 1996 (Box 22)
      - North American Manufacturing Research Conference, May 22, 1996 (Box 22)
      - Speeches, not dated, 1 folder (Box 22)
      - Speech Engagements, 1996 (Box 22)
      - Speech Schedule, ca., 1996 (Box 22)
  - Computer Printouts of Speeches, 1988-1994; 3 linear feet
    Computer Printouts of Speeches are printouts for the years 1988 to 1990 and 1992 to 1994. As such, they are often duplicates to the Speeches and Accompanying Materials series, but hold none of the contextual data. Most are dated, but there is no documentation as to whether this is a printout date or the date of creation. Researchers should note that many of the printouts are also available electronically, along with relevant data about them, in the Digital Documents subgroup. While this may on the surface seem redundant, preserving versions demonstrates some of the ways Duderstadt's office functioned, particularly in the evolving years of electronic record keeping. It becomes evident when the paper series are considered alongside the digital versions, that Duderstadt's office became over the years, more and more committed to functioning wholly in the electronic realm. Finally, since the papers were not processed at an item level, keeping these diverse versions offers the best likelihood that the collection will fairly comprehensively hold most of Duderstadt's speeches for this period.
    - 1988-1989
      - Parent's Orientation, September 4, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Leadership Network, September 6, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Leadership Network (b), September 6, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Graduate Student Welcome, September 8, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Minority Students Welcome, September 8, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Dean / Executive Officers Kickoff 2.0, September 11, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Fall Weekend, September 23, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Rackham 50th (a), September 30, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Rackham 50th (b), September 30, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Faculty Awards, October 3, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Historically Black Colleges and Universities Remarks, October 5, 1988 (Box 5)
      - "Home", October 5, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Student Inaugural Address, October 6, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Student Inauguration 1.5, October 6, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Inauguration, October 6, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Inauguration 1.2, October 6, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Inauguration 1.3, October 6, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Inauguration Remarks List, October 6, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Medical Center Reception, October 17, 1988 (Box 5)
      - 3-M Visit, October 18, 1988 (Box 5)
      - UM-Flint Science Bldg Dedication, October 20, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Alumni Talk - Short, October 22, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Leadership Network, October 28, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Booth Newspapers, October 29, 1988 (Box 5)
      - New Detroit Presentation, November 3, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Judaic Studies, November 15, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Medical Education, November 21, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Football Bust, November 28, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Commencement, December 18, 1988 (Box 5)
      - UM-Flint Commencement, December 22, 1988 (Box 6)
      - Big Ten Championship, December 29, 1988 (Box 6)
      - Listen and Learn Talk, January 12, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Martin Luther King Day - Unity March, January 16, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Martin Luther King Day - Opening, January 16, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Martin Luther King Day - Science / Manpower, January 16, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Martin Luther King Day - Business & Finance, January 16, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Martin Luther King Day - Closing, January 16, 1989 (Box 6)
      - CBS Good Morning Show, February 3, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Detroit Economic Club (a), February 13, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Detroit Economic Club (b), February 13, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Dedication of Canham Natatorium, February 17, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Congressional Breakfast, March 1, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Michigan Legislature, March 14, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Pow-Wow '89, March 18, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Honors Convocation, March 19, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Women's Issues, March 28, 1989 (Box 6)
      - PIF Remarks, March 28, 1989 (Box 6)
      - IPPS Welcome, March 29, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Legatus Talk, March 30, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Mortar Board, April 1, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Student Recognition Awards, April 3, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Welcome Home, April 4, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Penn State, April 6, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Phi Beta Kappa, April 8, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Alumni Satellite Breakfast, April 9, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Basketball Bust (a), April 10, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Basketball Bust (b), April 10, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Coaches Reception, April 19, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Senate Appropriations, April 24, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Senate Republican Caucus, April 25, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Commencement- - Rain, April 29, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Commencement - Spring, April 29, 1989 (Box 6)